ingamenow.com 2009-02-26

# Privacy

InGameNow is a social media network for sports fans. The site lets people remain current with their favorite leagues, teams, and athletes utilizing relevant sports content submitted by other community members and other sources. To accomplish this, our users create their own profiles, which display some personal information to other members and visitors. This allows our users to identify each other and expand their personal network of contacts. InGameNow members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them via the website, SMS, WAP and Instant Messaging ("Service").

InGameNow cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at info@ingamenow.com.

 **Information Collection and Use by InGameNow**

InGameNow collects user submitted information such as name, email address, age, and other information to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the InGameNow service. InGameNow also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, and geographical location in order to assist users in finding those topics of interest to the user and ease communication between community members.

InGameNow also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, cookie information, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. User Profile information including members' pictures, user names, and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the InGameNow social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join InGameNow, to add users to members' contacts networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on InGameNow with each other through the InGameNow service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter, or news regarding the service, though users may choose not to receive email of this type. From time to time, InGameNow, or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on InGameNow. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members InGameNow members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. InGameNow stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. InGameNow does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from InGameNow may contact InGameNow to request the removal of their information from our database.

You may prevent InGameNow email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK INVITE" to info@inGameNow.com. Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.

 **Use of Cookies**

InGameNow uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same promotions and advertisements, and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from InGameNow in order to use most functions on the site.

 **Links**

InGameNow contains links to sites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

 **Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs?, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forum that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

 **Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

InGameNow users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.

 **Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by InGameNow or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by InGameNow and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Security**

InGameNow member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. InGameNow takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on InGameNow, please contact us at info@ingamenow.com.

 **Sharing and Disclosure of Information InGameNow Collects**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, InGameNow will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by InGameNow, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the InGameNow Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

 **In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event that InGameNow is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

 **Special Note to International Users**

InGameNow is hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing InGameNow from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of InGameNow, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

 **Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

 **Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: info@ingamenow.com
